salsastore.com 2017-06-06

# Salsa® Jeans | Clothing and Accessories for Women & Men

**SALSA PRIVACY POLICY**

Welcome to www.salsastore.com. This Privacy Policy applies when you visit and surf www.salsastore.com (“Site”) without purchasing any product and/or when you use the services provided for purchasing products on this Site. By using this Site, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not want to accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy, please do not use this Site.  
Since personal data of users and customers of this Site (collectively “Users”) may be processed in Portugal, any such processing of personal data will be conducted in compliance with the Portuguese Data Protection.

**1\. OUR POLICY**

Everyone has the right to the protection of his/her personal data.

SALSA respects users' right to be informed about the collection and processing of their personal data.

As the controller of personal data, SALSA independently determines the purposes and means by which your personal data is processed, including all security measures. SALSA independently ensures that personal data is processed in Portugal in a correct and lawful manner and in accordance with good practice.

In processing data that can personally identify you, directly or indirectly, we apply the principle of strict necessity. For this reason, this Site has been designed in such a way that the use of your personal data will be minimal and will not exceed the original purpose for which your personal data was collected and/or processed. In particular, we do not disclose your identity when the purpose for which your personal data is being processed can be achieved by using anonymous aggregate information.

This Privacy Policy is intended to provide you with all the information you need in order to understand our privacy practices. However, if you have any question regarding our privacy practices and this Privacy Policy, please contact us at the following e-mail address: [customer.care@salsa.pt](mailto:customer.care@salsa.pt)

We do not sell products or services for purchase by children although we may sell children’s products or services for purchase by adults. If you are under 18, you may use this Site only with the consent of a parent or guardian.

**2\. WHO PROCESSES YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

For organizational and operational purposes only, SALSA has appointed certain entities that will also process personal data of Users of this Site on the Data Controllers’ behalf (“Data Processors”). Such purposes are strictly connected to the performance of services provided on this Site by SALSA, including the sale of products. The above-mentioned Data Processors have been chosen by SALSA because of their experience in processing personal data, their sufficient guarantees with respect to compliance with applicable laws and regulations, as well as the technical security measures adopted by them in connection with the processing of personal data. In processing personal data of Users of this Site, our Data Processors will act only in accordance with instructions provided by SALSA. We regularly verify that our Data Processors comply with our instructions and that they provide sufficient guarantees with respect to their compliance with applicable laws and regulations.

**3\. HOW DO WE USE PERSONAL DATA AND FOR WHAT PURPOSES**

Your personal data is collected and processed by SALSA for purposes which are strictly connected to the use of this Site, its services and the purchase of products on this Site. However, your personal data may also be used for other processing operations within the limits of such purposes. In particular, your personal data may be processed for the following purposes:

a) when you are executing purchasing procedures for products sold on this Site, including conclusion of an agreement for the purchase of products, we collect your personal data (for example, password, size, e-mail address, address for delivery, credit card numbers for payments and telephone numbers) on your order form only for the purpose of selling, picking and shipping the products ordered by you;

b) when you request service assistance, we collect your personal data (for example, your first and last names, e-mail address) for purposes strictly necessary to provide you with SALSA online Customer Service relevant to this Site and to the purchase of products on this Site;

c) when you request technical assistance, we collect your personal data in order to provide you with information on net-surfing, Internet browsing or viewing and downloading web pages; or

d) when creating and sharing your Wish List, we process your personal data in order to customize our services for the purchase of products on the Site;

e) when you save a shipping address, we process personal data in order to simplify the drawing up of your orders if done in the future.

SALSA will process your personal data generally by electronic means; however, in certain circumstances, paper-based means may be used (for example, when the processing of your personal data is required for the prevention of fraud against us).

Your personal data is stored in a way which allows SALSA to identify you for the period that is strictly necessary for the original purposes for which such personal data are collected and subsequently processed, except as specifically provided herein, all in accordance with applicable laws.

Please report any changes to your personal data to the e-mail address: [customer.care@salsa.pt](mailto:customer.care@salsa.pt) in order to ensure that your personal data is always accurate and kept up-to-date.

Except as provided herein, your personal data will not be disclosed to third parties for purposes not permitted by law or without your explicit consent. Your personal data may only be communicated to identified third parties when it is necessary to process an order placed by you. For example, your personal data is disclosed to natural persons or legal entity to (i) perform electronic payment services, through credit/debit cards, (ii) process all sales of products; (iii) pick, pack and ship products; (iv) issue invoices for the sales of products; (v) collect payments for the sales of products from customers, and (vi) process all returns of products from customers. Moreover, your personal data may be disclosed to the police or to judicial authorities, in compliance with applicable laws and regulations and upon a formal request by such authorities for example for the purposes of preventing a fraud against us (anti-fraud services). Data Processors will also have access to your personal data, as stated in Section 2 of this Privacy Policy, for the specific purposes stated in that Section. In all the above circumstances, your consent for data processing will not be specifically requested.

We wish to inform you that SALSA processes its Users’ personal data for purposes that are strictly connected to the supply of services through this Site, the execution of contracts related to the sale and purchase of products on this Site.

SALSA may have access to third parties' personal data which is directly disclosed by its Users to SALSA, for instance when a User buys a product to be sent to a friend, when the user who pays the purchase price for such product is different from the recipient of such product, or when a User wishes to recommend to a friend a service provided through this Site or the sale of a particular product posted on this Site.

In all cases involving the disclosure of information of a third party, you must obtain the consent of such individuals before disclosing their personal data to us and have informed said individuals about this Privacy Policy. You will be the only person liable in connection with the disclosure of information and data relevant to such third parties and with any other incompatible and unlawful use of such data if they have not provided you with their consent.

We may have access to your or third parties’ sensitive data (i.e. personal data allowing the disclosure of racial or ethnic origin, religious, philosophical, sex life, health) only in the case such data is directly disclosed by Users to SALSA. Please remember that any disclosure of sensitive data is not necessary for the services offered through this Site and any sensitive data will be cancelled if found. In all cases involving the disclosure of sensitive data to us, you will be the only person liable in connection with the disclosure and any illegal use of them by third party.

You agree to indemnify, defend and hold SALSA and its respective affiliates harmless from any liability, loss, claims and expenses, including reasonable attorneys’ fees, arising from or related to any unauthorized disclosure of personally identifiable information of third parties or to any disclosure and use of your or third parties’ sensitive data.

**4\. WHAT HAPPENS IF YOU DO NOT DISCLOSE YOUR PERSONAL DATA?**

4.1 Except as provided in the following section 4.2, the personal data we request you provide to us, including your e-mail address, your address, your credit/debit card numbers and your telephone number, is necessary for the processing of your order for the purchase of products on this Site to carry out obligations arising out of applicable laws and regulations or to supply other services provided through this Site upon your request.

4.2 Your refusal to provide certain personal data may prevent us from processing your order for the purchase of products sold on the Site or from providing other services through this Site such as Salsa Online Store Customer Service, use of the Wish List, or recommending a product to a friend.

Your failure to provide personal data may justify our refusal to process your order for the purchase of products sold or to provide one or more services through this Site.

The disclosure of personal data to us other than that required in order to fulfill legal or contractual obligations or to provide the services requested by you is optional and does not have any effect on your use of this Site and its services or on the purchase of products on this Site.

We will inform you if the personal data we ask you to provide is necessary or optional by marking with an asterisk (*) the information that is necessary. Your failure to disclose optional personal data will not result in any obligation or penalty to you.

The disclosure of sensitive data is never requested and always not allowed.

**5\. TO WHOM YOUR PERSONAL DATA WILL BE DISCLOSED**

Your personal data may be disclosed to third parties who provide specific services as Data Processors on behalf of SALSA or who autonomously process personal data collected by SALSA in connection with the performance of a contract for the purchase of products on this Site. Any such disclosure will be conducted, in each instance, without exceeding the original purposes for which your personal data was collected and subsequently processed.

In addition, your personal data may be disclosed to third parties in order to (1) comply with applicable laws, (2) respond to governmental and judiciary inquiries, (3) comply with valid legal process, and (4) protect the rights or property of SALSA.

In the event there is a change in the corporate structure of SALSA including, without limitation, by merger, consolidation, sale, liquidation, or transfer of substantial assets, SALSA may, in its sole discretion, transfer, sell or assign personal data collected on and through this Site, including, without limitation, personally identifiable information and aggregate information concerning Users, to one or more affiliated or unaffiliated third parties.

In any event your personal data will not be disclosed to third parties without you being informed or without your consent, when such consent is required by law, except as provided herein.

**6\. SECURITY MEASURES**

We have adopted security measures to protect personal data against accidental or unlawful destruction, loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access and against other unlawful forms of data processing, as provided in this Privacy Policy.

Nevertheless, SALSA cannot guarantee that the security measures adopted for the protection of this Site and the transmission of data and information through this Site will prevent or exclude any risk of unauthorized access to or loss of data. It is advisable that your computer be equipped with software devices for the protection of network data transmission and receipt (such as updated antivirus systems) and that your Internet service provider take appropriate measures for the security of network data transmission (such as firewalls and anti-spam filtering).

**7\. COOKIES**

SALSA uses automatic systems of data collection, such as cookies. A cookie is a device transmitted to the hard drive of an Internet user. While cookies do not contain intelligible information, they allow us to link an Internet user to personal information provided by such user through this Site. Cookies are disseminated by our servers and no one may gain access to the information contained therein. Only SALSA processes information collected by cookies, in a collective and anonymous way, in order to optimize its services and this Site for the needs and preferences of Users and to prepare customized web pages.

We disseminate cookies in connection with functions such as browsing the catalogue, purchasing products on-line and supplying services reserved to registered users.

As you may know, each Internet browser allows the deletion of cookies after each session. Your Internet browser contains instructions on how to carry out these procedures of deletion. Please access the appropriate instructions section on your Internet browser if you wish to delete cookies.

Your acceptance of our automatic procedures of collection of data and the use of cookies is necessary to take advantage of many features and services offered through this Site, including the purchase of products. If you set your browser to block or delete cookies, we cannot guarantee that you will have access to all the features and services offered through this Site (for example, your computer may not be able to display the image of the product you are in the process of purchasing).

**8\. YOUR RIGHT TO ACCESS PERSONAL DATA AND FURTHER RIGHTS**

You are entitled to obtain, at any time, confirmation from SALSA as to whether or not data relating to you is being processed, even if not yet registered, and the communication of any such data in an intelligible form.

Moreover, you are entitled to receive from SALSA information on the source from which we received your personal data; the purposes and means of processing your personal data; the logic involved in any electronic data processing; information regarding the data controllers and the data processors and the names of subjects and categories of subjects to whom your personal data may be disclosed or who may access your personal data (for example, the names of data processors). You can also find the above information in this Privacy Policy.

You are entitled to obtain at any time from SALSA:

a) the updating, rectification or integration of your personal data;

b) the deletion, transformation into anonymous form or blocking of your personal data, which is processed in violation of the law, including when the storage of data is not necessary for the purposes for which it has been collected and subsequently processed;

c) the confirmation that the operations under letters a) and b) have been reported to whom the data were disclosed or disseminated, except when it becomes impossible to do so or if it means exceeding the protection of the right you are claiming.

You are entitled to object, in all or in part:

a) for legitimate reasons, to the processing of your personal data, even if it is related to the purposes for which it was collected;

b) to the processing of your personal data for advertising or direct marketing purposes or in order to sell products or to carry out marketing research or commercial communications.

You may freely and at any time exercise your rights, provided that you do so in compliance with applicable laws and regulations, by sending your request to SALSA at the following e-mail address [customer.care@salsa.pt](mailto:customer.care@salsa.pt)

**9\. CONTACTS**

If you wish to receive further information regarding our privacy practices, please contact us by e-mail at [customer.care@salsa.pt](mailto:customer.care@salsa.pt)

**10\. GOVERNING LAW**

The processing of personal data by SALSA will be conducted in compliance with applicable Portuguese Laws.

**11\. MODIFICATION AND UPDATING**

SALSA may amend or update from time to time all or any part of this Privacy Policy, whether or not required by a change in the applicable laws and regulation.

Our users will be notified of any amendment to or update of our Privacy Policy on our homepage. All amendments and updates will become effective upon publication on this section of this Site. You should regularly access this section of this Site in order to review the most recent and updated version of our Privacy Policy.

**12\. SALSA STAR**  
Salsa Star is a loyalty programme offered by SALSA. 

Conditions of Use for the Salsa Star Community: 

By becoming part of the Salsa Star Community, the user accepts the present Service Conditions (this “Agreement”), independently of registering or not as a member of the Salsa Star Community (Member). Salsa Star services consist in the Salsa Star Community and in the functionalities and promotions it makes available.

If you would like to become a Member, communicate with other Members and become a user of this Service, then please read the present Agreement and follow the instructions for the registration process. The present agreement defines the mandatory legal terms for participation and may be modified by Salsa whenever necessary. All alterations shall take effect after Salsa announces them in the Salsa Star Community. You may also receive a copy of this agreement by sending an e-mail to: [customer.care@salsa.pt](mailto:customer.care@salsa.pt) , Subject: "Service Conditions Agreement"

1\. PROPERTY RIGHTS OF THE SERVICE  
Salsa Star possesses and reserves all property rights pertaining to these Services. The Services contain material protected by copyright, commercial brands and other confidential information (Intellectual Property Rights) of Salsa Star and of the respective partners, in accordance with Salsa, including the members of Salsa Star. With regard to Intellectual Property which is part of the public domain or to which access authorisation has been granted, the user may not copy, change, publish, transmit, distribute, execute, present or sell any Intellectual Property, being that the supply of any of these through the Service does not transfer to the user or to any third party, any rights, titles or interests in or for Intellectual Property, including, without limitations, any Intellectual Property Rights in any Contents and material included in the Salsa Star Community.

2\. CONTENT PUBLISHED IN THE SERVICE  
The user understands and accepts that Salsa Star may (but is not obligated to) review any classified ads, contents, information, Intellectual Property, material, messages, photographs, videos URL’s, profiles, etc., (collectively, "Content") downloaded, published or presented (from hereon forward, "published") in the Service, and eliminate or refuse to publish any Content, including but not limited to, any content that in the sole understanding of Salsa Star violates the present Agreement or that may be offensive or illegal, or that may violate the rights and jeopardise or threaten the security of other Members or third parties. The user is held solely responsible for the Content published by them in the Services and transmitted to other Members or third parties. By publishing Contents in any area of the Services, the user automatically concedes, claiming and guaranteeing that they have the right, to Salsa Star an international and irrevocable licence, lifelong, non-exclusive, without the right to payment of copyright and pays in totality to reproduce, distribute, publicly present, execute (including through digital audio transmission) and use the Contents in other ways, as well as prepare work derived from or incorporate in other works, the before-mentioned Contents and concede and authorise sub-licences of the said Contents. In addition, the user claims and guarantees that they possess the right to publish Content and shall not publish illegal or prohibited Content, as well as not infringe, if unduly acquired, violate or transgress any third party rights (including, without limitations, any intellectual property rights). The following is a partial list of illegal or prohibited Content on the Internet Page ("Prohibited Contents"). Salsa Star reserves the right (but is not obligated to) investigate and take the necessary legal measures, in its understanding, against any individual who violates this clause, including, without limitations, the removal of the offensive Content from the Service and cessation of the relationship with the violators.

Prohibited contents include those which:

a) are clearly offensive to the online community, such as Content which promotes racism, fanaticism, hate or physical offences of any kind against any group or individual; 

b) imply the sending of junk mail, chain letters or unsolicited e-mails or spamming;

c) promote false or misleading information or promote illegal activities or abusive, threatening, obscene, defamatory or slanderous conduct;

d) Request passwords or personal identification information of any kind for the commercial or illicit finalities of other users and involving commercial and/or sales activities without previous written consent, such as competitions, bets, exchanges, publicity or pyramid schemes. e) are in any other way abusive to the Salsa Star programme according to the terms defined.

3\. ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATION  
Communication between the User and Salsa Star is carried out by electronic means or by SMS.

4\. Salsa, Irmãos Vila Nova, S.A. (hereon forward “Salsa”), is the promoter of the Salsa Star programme.

1\. Objective

1.1) The Salsa Star programme allows clients to be rewarded for the preference they demonstrate in purchasing Salsa products, or any others that may be stipulated, through access to prizes, privileges, benefits and other products or services, at the various Salsa store locations.

1.2) Any individual who is a Salsa client, 18 years or older and is not a Salsa employee may participate in the programme.

1.3) The prizes, privileges, benefits and other products or services in effect at the time shall be communicated on-line in the Salsa Star Community, at [www.salsastore.com](http://www.salsastore.com/)

1.4) Salsa may also, at any moment and without previous notice alter the prizes, privileges, benefits and other products or services.

1.5) The operating conditions of the programme, foreseen in the present regulations and part of the legal notices published on the site [www.salsastore.com](http://www.salsastore.com/), come into effect on February 1st 2012. This date may however be altered in function of the evolution or development introduced in the operating model of programme, safeguarding the legitimate interests of the members. 

2\. Validity / Characteristics

2.1) The Salsa Star programme is of unlimited duration. However, Salsa reserves the right to cancel, alter or substitute the programme and the respective regulations and legal notices by communicating the situation at least 30 days in advance, by publishing this information in the Salsa Star Community on the site [www.salsastore.com](http://www.salsastore.com/). The obtainment of benefits may only take place 30 days after the date announced to be the end date of the programme.

3\. Membership

3.1) Any client, in a personal capacity, may become a member of the Salsa Star programme on the site [www.salsastore.com](http://www.salsastore.com/), in the respective registration area, or in participating Salsa stores.

3.2) The use of the internet site [www.salsastore.com](http://www.salsastore.com/) implies the participants having knowledge and expressly accepting the conditions of use (Legal  notices) and of the present regulations.

3.3) All individuals who correctly registered in the Salsa Star programme on the site [www.salsastore.com](http://www.salsastore.com/)  and were attributed a user name and password for the registered clients area are members of the Salsa Star programme.

3.4) According to the terms of the legislation in effect relative to the protection of computerised personal information, the information gathered by Salsa shall be computer processed and stored, so that it may be analysed, decided upon and managed relative to the services to be provided and the addresses used to send commercial information regarding the Salsa Star programme.

3.5) The right to access the information registered about each user is a recognised right of the subscribers, as long as they are duly identified. Furthermore, they may request that their information be corrected and/or eliminated.

3.6) Members of the Salsa Star programme may end their participation in the programme by communicating this information through express communication which includes the identification information supplied at the time of registration in the Salsa Star programme and supplied to Salsa. This request can be made by e-mail to the address: [customer.care@salsa.pt](mailto:customer.care@salsa.pt) or mailed directly to Salsa Star at the address: Avenida das Indústrias, nº 511 Apartado 7079 - 4760-725 Ribeirão, V.N.F. Portugal.

4\. Salsa Star Programme

4.1) The Salsa Star programme is supported by a computer application available on the site  [www.salsastore.com](http://www.salsastore.com/), through which clients can accumulate points in function of Salsa purchases made in-store and through the use of the site [www.salsastore.com](http://www.salsastore.com/)

In addition to the accumulation of points, the Salsa Star programme allows each member to obtain benefits, prizes and advantages, to be decided and announced during the Salsa Star programme on [www.salsastore.com](http://www.salsastore.com/).

4.2) The Salsa Star programme allows its members to have exclusive access to or with particular conditions, the benefits and offers proposed at the time.

4.3) The member information in the Salsa Star programme is personal and non-transferrable. The client’s identification may be requested to ensure the security of the system. Salsa recommends that all users save their information in a secure manner.

4.4) Salsa reserves the right to not accept or attribute points to members of the Salsa Star programme whenever fraud, undue use or commercial use is detected or whenever the technical identification is not within the parameters stipulated by the system.

4.5) The Salsa Star programme does not have a maximum limit for the accumulation of points.

4.6) Salsa Star points expire within one year, the start date being the date on which the points were acquired. Salsa is not obligated to previously notify the member when said points expire.

4.7) The registration and later use of the Salsa Star programme assumes the user has knowledge of and accepts the Regulations of the programme, its general conditions for the attribution of points and legal notices relative to Community membership.

4.8) Salsa cannot be held responsible for the loss or theft of identification information in the Salsa Star programme, and therefore any possible re-registration shall be made without attribution of the previously accumulated points. The information recovered by the network of Salsa stores shall be returned to the holders. It is recommended that the information be updated (name, address, telephone), on the site [www.salsastore.com](http://www.salsastore.com/) or by mail to: Programa Salsa Star – Avenida das Indústrias, nº 511 Apartado 7079 4760-725 Ribeirão, V.N.F. Portugal.

4.9) Salsa reserves the right to cancel or expire a registration in the Salsa Star programme due to non-fulfilment of the terms and conditions for participation and those registrations in which fraud or undue use is detected.  

4.10) Accumulated points which have expired, may no longer be used and shall be automatically removed from the personal account of each of the users. 

5) Salsa Points

5.1) Salsa Star points are issued by Salsa stores participating in the programme through the use of the computer system which supports the programme and available for updated consultation by the member (dependent on the synchronisation of the computer systems, which may take place over a 48 hour period) in the private access area of each member on the site [www.salsastore.com](http://www.salsastore.com/) (History of Purchases). 

5.2) The attributed points are valid for one year, starting from the day each one was attributed or attained and are used according to the chronological order of their respective validity expiring.

5.3) Salsa Star points cannot be converted into cash, nor do they constitute a method of payment, in titles of the same, for any articles.

5.4) Salsa Star points are personal and non-transferrable. 

6) Attribution of points in the Salsa Star programme

6.1) Salsa Star points are attributed in accordance with the information contained in promotional campaigns (by e-mail, SMS and in-store) and in effect at each particular time on the internet site, in function of:

a) Purchases carried out in participating Salsa stores – with a correspondence of 1€ in purchases = 1 point in the community;

b) Promotional systems of personalised point attribution (promotional campaigns);

c) On-line interactions

d) Recruited friends (registered on-line to Salsa Star through the Share&Win client invitation) = 25 points

6.2) The development of the specified promotional campaigns may allow, during specific periods of time, for the attribution of Salsa Star Points in quantities different from those previously stipulated, the attribution of a bonus according to determined criteria and communicated on a case-by-case basis, or points may not be attributed when there exist benefits of other advantages in obtaining offers in the Salsa Star programme.

6.3) The reward promotions and processes described may be cancelled at any moment without previous notification.

6.4) The accumulation of Salsa Star points results in moving up the 5 different levels:

a) Level 1 (1 star clients) <150 points;

b) Level 2 (2 star clients) = 150 to 399 points;

c) Level 3 (3 star clients) = 400 to 799 points;

d) Level 4 (4 star clients) = 800 to 1299 points;

e) Level 5 (5 star clients) ≥ 1300 points; 

6.5) The attribution of Salsa Star points may exclude the possibility of acquisition of benefits related to other programmes promoted by Salsa or in which Salsa participates, through a clear communication with the client regarding the programme or campaign which resulted in the exclusion.

7) Use of Salsa points – Benefits

7.1) The conditions for the use of points are regulated according to the conditions available at the site [www.salsastore.com](http://www.salsastore.com/), in effect at the time, or any other information Salsa issues to that effect. 

7.2) All benefits are limited to the conditions in effect at the time and existing stock.

7.3) Salsa reserves the right to substitute the prizes with identical offers or ones of a similar value.

7.4) The Salsa Star programme makes available the following benefits, in accordance with the conditions in effect at the time:

a) Access to the benefits associated with campaigns, in effect at the time and which may be different for each Salsa Star level. 

b) Access to raffles and promotions, in effect at the time and which may be different for each Salsa Star level.

c) Exclusive access to information regarding the programme;

d) Birthday Discount (5% for 2 star clients, 10% for 3 star clients, 15% for 4 star clients and 20% for 5 star clients).The discount is valid for one purchase at participating points of sale. The discount can't be combined with other campaigns or discounts and it isn't valid for promotions or sales neither in the purchase of gift-voucher/e-gifts. This benefit is only applicable to clients who have a valid email address and mobile number in their client record and who have authorised Salsa to contact them. It is valid from the day before the Customer´s birthday until 15 days after.

e) Happy Day Online (valid for 3, 4 and 5 star clients – 10%, 15% and 20% respectively). The discount is valid for one purchase only at [www.salsastore.com](http://www.salsastore.com/). The discount can't be combined with other campaigns or discounts and it isn't valid for promotions or sales neither in the purchase of gift-voucher/e-gifts. This benefit is only applicable to clients who have a valid email address and mobile number in their client record and who have authorised Salsa to contact them.

f) Level-up Discount - 10% (valid for all levels). The discount is valid for one purchase at participating points of sale and not cumulative with other campaigns/promotions. For this discount, a change in level is considered to be valid; however recovery of a previous level within a period of less than three months is not valid. This benefit is only applicable to clients who have a valid email address and mobile number in their client record and who have authorised Salsa to contact them.

g) Free Shipping and Handling from the On-line Store (for 4 and 5 star clients) (valid only for European Union)

h) Christmas gift for all 5 star clients (clients which have or acquired 5 stars up to December 24th of the year respective to the campaign).

7.5) The delivery of prizes which may be attributed is subject to the conditions in effect at the time.

8) By registering in Salsa Star, the Member automatically registers in the Share&Win service. With this service, when friends are invited, the Member wins 25 points (invitations before June 10, 2013 earn 5 points) for each friend who registers in the Salsa Star programme. The member also receives a voucher in the amount equivalent to 10% of the amount paid by each friend in their first on-line purchase after registering through Share&Win. The 10% is calculated using the amount paid by the friend, in other words, net amount after discounts. The 10% is offered as long as the purchase occurs in the month following their registration. The discount can't be combined with other campaigns or discounts and it isn't valid for promotions or sales neither in the purchase of gift-voucher/e-gifts. 

If Salsa detects exploitation/fraud, the Member must return the amount unduly received and may be forbidden from taking part in the Salsa Star Community.  

Whenever a Member registers in Salsa Star through Share&Win, they agree to Salsa sharing with the friend who invited them, the fact that they indeed did register. This permission is necessary so that the friend may win 25 points.

Whenever a Member registers in Salsa Star through Share&Win, they will receive a 15% discount on their first on-line purchase. The discount can't be combined with other campaigns or discounts and it isn't valid for promotions or sales neither in the purchase of gift-voucher/e-gifts. By registering, the member accepts that Salsa shares with the friend who invited them, the value of their first purchase. This authorisation is necessary so that the friend may win a voucher in the amount of 10% of their first purchase (net value). The discount can't be combined with other campaigns or discounts and it isn't valid for promotions or sales neither in the purchase of gift-voucher/e-gifts. 

9) Participating Salsa stores 

9.1) The accumulation of points is valid at Salsa’s online store and all Salsa stores in Portugal, Spain, France, Germany, Luxemburg and Angola, including outlets, except ECIs, Lafayette Galleries and other department stores.

9.2) The discounts are valid at Salsa’s online store and all Salsa stores in Portugal, Spain, France, Luxemburg, Germany and Angola, expect ECIs and other department stores.  

10) Suggestions or complaints

10.1) Possible suggestions or complaints may be directed to the e-mail address [www.salsastore.com](http://www.salsastore.com/), or by mail to: Programa Salsa Star Avenida das Indústrias, nº 511 Apartado 7079 4760-725 Ribeirão, V.N.F. Portugal.
